mbaonline.com 2013-12-20

# Privacy Policy - OnlineMBA.com

The following privacy statement depicts OnlineMBA.com’s collection and utilization process of personal information you provide to us.

#### Personal Information Collection and Utilization

While you use OnlineMBA.com services, we maintain the right to collect personal information from you as follows:

  * Contact Information; for example, your full name, contact phone number, email address
  * Demographic information; for example, your education background, zip code, probable graduation date

As is true of most websites, we maintain the right to collect information concerning your computer; for example, your browser service, IP address, referring/exit pages, and operating system.

With this information we act to:

  * Locate and make available online college degree programs and related information that matches your career aspirations, education goals, and online education search requirements.
  * Send you school information you have requested
  * Reply to customer service requests
  * Send you a relevant newsletter
  * Send you relevant marketing communications
  * Reply to your concerns and questions
  * Evaluate our Web OnlineMBA.com, marketing efforts, and business needs for future improvement
  * Research and analysis our market, business, etc.

#### Opt-Out Option

If you wish to opt-out of receiving marketing information from us, find and follow our unsubscribe instructions included in our email communications to you.

#### Information Sharing

The ways we emit your personal information to third parties are compliant with that which is described in this privacy statement. Under no circumstance will OnlineMBA.com sell acquired personal information to third parties for their disparate marketing purposes. In certain circumstances, we may provide your personal information to companies that provide OnlineMBA.com with business administration services; for instance, our email delivery service.

Additionally, the act of providing OnlineMBA.com with your personal information serves as you making an “inquiry” to and permitting us , our affiliates, and our third party marketing partners and/or vendors to contact you. This act also grants us and our affiliates permission to contact you via telephone for a limited time, regardless of your submission to a state or federal Do Not Call list as your inquiry is a legal exception to all Do Not Call stipulations.ÿ

We also maintain the right to release your submitted personal information when OnlineMBA.com merges, procures, or sells all or a percentage of its assets to a third party with your prior consent, and is required by law, such as in the case of a court order, to disclose said information when we consider, in good faith, such a disclosure is necessary to protect our constitutional rights, yours or another’s safety, probe fraud/fraudulent events, or adhere to a government request.

#### Privacy Statement Changes Notification

If changes in our information procedures are made, we may renew this privacy statement to reflect them. We suggest that you check this privacy policy occasionally to ensure your understanding of it is up-to-date.

#### Contacting OnlineMBA.com

Please send us all questions or concerns with respect to this privacy policy through our contact form.

Effective date: August 18, 2012
